AI's gonna start beating salespeople earlier than you'd think.
Not because they are better on the phone
or they're gonna sound better,
but simply because they do two things better than humans.
First is they're gonna get to leads faster,
meaning what normally takes a human maybe 20 minutes
or even two hours in the worst case scenario,
which is like 80% of businesses,
two days to get to their leads,
they'll be able to get to it in seconds.
The second thing is that if the person doesn't answer
the phone or doesn't respond back,
they're gonna do the other thing that humans don't do,
which is they're going to try again.
And they're gonna follow up and they're gonna follow up
perfectly for extended periods of time.
And so right now, one, incorporating AI
into your sales process is not a nice to have,
but a need to have.
And number two, always remember that today
is the worst it will ever be.